mightbenews.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy – Might Be News

_Last Updated: January 01, 2016_

Generally [MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/) (“Site” or “we”, “our” or “us”) does not collect, store, use or disclose any data collected with an intention to identify and/or contact a person such as: name, address, telephone number or e-mail address (hereinafter “PII”).

For [MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/), privacy is a top priority and we provide this Privacy Policy to outline our practices and procedures with respect to information collection and use to enable you to make an informed decision about sharing information with us.

**What does this Privacy Policy cover?**

This Privacy Policy applies to collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by us.  
Please be aware that, as part of the service provided by this Site, we may provide links to websites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party Web sites or applications. You should check the applicable privacy policies of such third-party Web sites or applications to determine how they handle any information they collect from you.

**What information does** **[MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/) collect and how is it used? Does ****[MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/) disclose information to third parties?**

We may collect any or all of the following three types of information: (i) traffic or clickstream data, or (ii) non-personally identifiable information (for example: IP address, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access dates and times, referring website addresses, online transactions and browsing and search activity) (“Non-PII”). Our collection and use of each type of data is described below, as well as the ways (if any) in which the data may be shared with third parties or subsidiaries or affiliates of [MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/).

(a) Traffic or Clickstream Data (“Clickstream Data”). Clickstream Data consists of traffic and usage data that is not personally identifiable. We do not supplement or combine Clickstream Data with any PII. We may share Clickstream Data we collect with certain selected third parties and [MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/), but only in anonymous form. Notwithstanding the foregoing, such third parties and [MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/) may combine such Clickstream Data with any PII that you choose to give to such third parties or [MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/) when registering with their websites. We collect Clickstream Data regarding use of our services by observing browser functions and the files (pages) you access. For example, our servers collect information about the site to which you may redirect to in order to enable us to calculate and receive payments from our business partners. In addition, we may use Clickstream Data to better design our services.

(b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information. As part of our on-going efforts to ensure the best possible experience for all users of the Site, we may use log files, web beacons and cookies to collect Non-PII from the Site, browsers, advertisers and third-party sites. “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site and collect data including: your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, click data and types of advertisements viewed. “Web beacons” are electronic files used to track your navigation of a website or collection of sites, the completion of transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior. “Cookies” are files (e.g. flash browser objects) that are stored on your Internet enabled device (which includes your computer, BlackBerry or other PDA). Cookies are used to improve the experience web users have when they see web advertisements and ensure that when a web user clicks on an advertisement, they are sent to the correct click-through destination. We may use Cookies for purposes which may include, without limitation, to estimate the total reach of any of our advertisers, how frequently you return to the Site, as well as to streamline experiences of users of our Site. Cookies are also an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for ways to improve our services. All information collected by Cookies, Web beacons and Log files are Non-PII.

There are two classes of Cookies based on how long they remain on your system: (i) “Session Cookies” may be used only during your visit to the Site and are erased once you close your browser, and (ii) “Persistent Cookies” (if applicable) remain on your browser for one (1) year from your last visit to the Site and enable us to remember you on subsequent visits to the Site and provide more relevant content to you on such Site.

There are many misconceptions about Cookies, some of which we will try to address in this policy. Cookies cannot erase your hard drive or otherwise damage your computer and do not tell us an e-mail address or any other PII. We do not and cannot use Cookies or web beacons to retrieve PII from your computer. Most internet browsers and browser add-ons allow you to adjust their settings to allow you to automatically refuse Cookies either generally or from specific sites. To adjust these settings, we suggest that you contact the supplier of your browser and browser add-ons for more information.

A useful resource on understanding Cookies may be found at [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

(c) Third Party Advertising. We have relationships with third-party advertising companies to drive traffic to and to serve ads on our Site. We share Clickstream Data and Non-PII with such advertising companies. Such companies may also collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of Cookies and other technology and any personally identifiable information you may choose to give in registering and transacting with any website linked to such ads. Although we choose our business partners and clients carefully, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of these third-party advertisers to determine how they handle any information they collect from you.

**Is data stored by** **[MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/) secure?**

We employ reasonable measures to ensure the security of all information and we routinely evaluate our practices to identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when communicating with us.

**How can I learn about changes to this privacy policy?**

We may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the revised Privacy Policy and the date the Privacy Policy was last updated on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you use this Site to make sure you understand how your information will be used. It is the express will of the parties that this agreement and all related documents have been drawn up in English.

**How do I find out more about** **[MIGHTBENEWS.COM](http://mightbenews.com/) information practices?**

If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact us by e-mail at [info@mightbenews.com](mailto:info@mightbenews.com)
